Good morning.
(Sheldon:)If I could have everyone's
attention, please?
(Sheldon:)I know we're all eager
to get on the road to Big Sur,
(Sheldon:)so if we focus, I'm sure we can
get through this orientation
(Sheldon:)in under a half an hour.
(Sheldon:)Then it's just Q&A,
quiz, safety drills,
(Sheldon:)pose for commemorative
group photo and we're off.
(Leonard:)Don't worry. Just sit
next to me during the quiz,
(Leonard:)and you can copy my answers.
(Sheldon:)Raj?
(Sheldon:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I don't think so.
(Sheldon:)You've had your allotted
six ounces.
(Sheldon:)The first bathroom break
isn't until the Denny's
(Sheldon:)located near Bakersfield,
(Sheldon:)which is approximately
two and half hours away.
(Sheldon:)Remember, people, we're only as
strong as our weakest bladder.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)Nobody cares about
your Kegel exercises.
(Sheldon:)All right. We have
seven people, and two cars.
(Sheldon:)In the lead car,
driven by Leonard,
(Sheldon:)will be... myself,